James Thomas Edmondson-Jones

The Old Chapel Main Street Grasby, Lincolnshire DN38 6AH 07592533754

A graduate of Hull University with a BSc (Hons) in Computer Science. Experienced with learning and applying new skills, presenting information in a formal manner and working to set deadlines.

Employment History:

Deliveroo Rider (Hull Area)

January 2017 – September 2017 Salary: £5760 per annum pro rata

Key roles and responsibilities: Duties including collecting orders from specified restaurants, finding a safe and quick cycling route to the customer, cycling that route then finding the correct house or office and delivering the order.

Reason for leaving: Moved out of area

Research Assistant

September 2014 – July 2015

Sheffield Hallam University Howard Street Sheffield South Yorkshire

S1 1WB

Salary: £19,500 per annum pro rata

Key roles and responsibilities: Duties included the daily preparation of the metabolic kitchen and ensuring the sensory laboratory was prepared ready for the commencement of the research study. Delivering inductions to research participants and ensuring the completion of Visual Analogue Scales and Profile of Mood State (POMS) questionnaires. I also designed a database for the collection and storage of research data

Reason for leaving: Fixed term contract and move to Hull

Library/IT Assistant

January 2012 - September 2014

Caistor Arts and Heritage Centre 28 Plough Hill Caistor Lincolnshire

LN7 6LZ

Salary: Volunteer

Key roles and responsibilities: Duties included supervising the library as the only member of staff during the early evening period. The cataloguing of returned books using the library systems. Assisting members of the public in using the computer suite, tailoring my support and training based on the individual requirements of the customer. Dealing with requests and queries on a range of technical and IT related issues.

Reason for leaving: revision for A levels

Education

2:1 BSc (Hons)	Computer Science	Hull University	2018
A Level Grade C	Geography	Caistor	2015
		Grammar	
A Level Grade C	ICT	Caistor	2015
		Grammar	
A Level Grade D	Physics	Caistor	2015
		Grammar	
A Level Grade D	General Studies	Caistor	2015
		Grammar	
13 GCSE (A-C)	Including English,	Caistor	2013
	Maths, Physics,	Grammar	
	Biology, Chemistry		
	and ICT		

Other Qualifications/Achievements

- 2015 Laboratory Health & Safety Induction Sheffield Hallam University
- 2014 Data Protection West Lindsey Council
- 2014 Basic Health & Safety West Lindsey Council
- 2012 to 2014 Duke of Edinburgh Awards, Bronze, Silver & Gold
- 2013 National Citizenship Scheme
- 2011 National Science Competition

Interests

I am a hiker having completed all three levels of Duke of Edinburgh Award. I have been a member of a rowing club from the age of 14; enjoy playing rugby and clay pigeon shooting. I have recently enjoyed supporting a Doctoral research project in the sensory laboratories of Sheffield Hallam University.

Personal details

Date of birth: 11.10.1996

References

Stephanie Dale
Caistor Arts and Heritage Centre
28 Plough Hill
Caistor
Lincolnshire
LN7 6LZ

volunteers@28ploughhill.co.uk

Nick Robinson
Caistor Grammar School
Church Street
Caistor
Lincoln
LN7 6QJ

Nicholas.Robinson@caistorgrammar.com